Search for... 

[

Saudi ADHD Society

A Prosperous Life for People with ADHD](https://adhd.org.sa/en/ "← Saudi ADHD Society")

* Programs

[

Saudi ADHD Society

A Prosperous Life for People with ADHD](https://adhd.org.sa/en/ "← Saudi ADHD Society")

Navigation Menu

Navigation Menu

* Programs

Search for... 

1. [](https://adhd.org.sa/)
2. /
3. Privacy Policy

1. [](https://adhd.org.sa/)
2. /
3. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Thank you for visiting our website.

We believe that every visitor to this site has the right to complete privacy in-line with international standards, regardless of their level of technical competence or awareness of privacy practices. As such, we make the following promises:

Our Promises
------------

**No Cookies:** The Saudi ADHD Society website does not use any cookies, whether for functionality, tracking, or analytics, either for site visitors or logged-in users.

**No “Cookie Alternatives”:** This website does not use any other forms of persistent data storage for tracking purposes or otherwise. Emails sent from this site do not use tracking pixels.

**No IP Addresses Saved:** When you fill in a form on this site, we do not save any extra hidden information about you, your location, your device, or anything else.

**Protection of Minors:** In line with the (Saudi Arabian) Children and Incompetent’s Privacy Protection Policy, no personal identifiable information of minors or those otherwise incapable of responsible privacy decisions is collected via this website.

**Online support:** Our individual support sessions, which may be linked to in emails sent from this site, utilise Doxy — a secure telemedicine platform which meets worldwide security requirements. All experts delivering individual sessions online using Doxy follow clear privacy guidelines.

Full Disclosure
---------------

**Security Log Retention:** This site has internal and external firewalls that help protect against hacking attempts. These tools can see IP addresses of visitors, their country and city (but not exact location), as well as usernames of logged-in users. These data are kept for 30 days and then deleted.

**International Web Host:** This site is hosted by SiteGround on a server in Los Angeles, USA. This means that server logs and any information you explicitly submit via forms on this site are currently saved on a server (computer) outside of Saudi Arabia. While SiteGround is a well-known and secure web hosting provider, we aim to relocate to an alternative server inside Saudi Arabia by the first quarter of 2024.

Full Policy (Translation from Arabic)
-------------------------------------

We are committed to preserving your privacy to the utmost, in line with the following privacy policy:

* You have the right to know how any data you share with our website is used.
* We are committed to protecting the rights of all visitors and users of this site and are committed to preserving the confidentiality of the data. We have prepared this privacy policy to disclose our approach to data collection and dissemination on this website.
* We assure you that your privacy is a top priority, and we will only use your data in an appropriate manner that ensures your data security.
* We also confirm that this site is not engaged in any for-profit activities.
* We do not share personal data with any commercial entity except that which is clearly announced to the site user and with the user’s explicit consent.
* We absolutely do not utilize site user contact information to send messages with commercial or promotional content.
* We may use the data recorded on the site to create questionnaires and surveys in order to improve the site and provide a more user-friendly experience for visitors and users. We may also communicate with you when needed to offer you the opportunity to donate to philanthropic projects or for you see the latest project updates and charitable works by the society where this data helps us communicate with you, answer your queries, and respond to your requests as far as possible.
* We do not share this data with third parties unless they are required to complete your request, unless this is in the context of collective data used for statistical purposes and research, without including any data that may be used to inform you.
* Data and data are normally processed electronically through specific applications and programs, without the need for staff participation or access to such data.
* In exceptional cases (such as investigations and cases), the staff of the regulatory authorities or those who need to know them may be informed of them; subject to the provisions of the law and the orders of the judicial authorities.
* This Privacy Policy applies to all services and transactions made on this site except where specific services or transactions are provided that have a separate privacy policy not incorporated into this Privacy Policy.
* However, the site may contain links to other websites outside of our control and which are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites by using the links available on our site, you will be subject to the privacy policy of these sites, which may be different from this site’s policy, and which require you to read the respective privacy policies for those sites.
* This site may contain links to sites or portals that may use data protection methods and privacy that differ from the methods we use. We are not responsible for the content and privacy of other sites that are not hosted by this site and those sites are responsible for their data protection. We recommend referring to the individual Privacy Policies of those sites.
* In any event, we will not sell, lease or trade your data for the benefit of any third parties outside this site. At all times, we will maintain the privacy and confidentiality of all personal data we receive.
* Due to the tremendous development in the field of technology and the change in the scope of the laws relating to the internet, the site reserves the right to amend the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy at any time it deems appropriate. Any amendments to the privacy policy will be implemented on this page, and you will be informed of any modifications that are made.
* To protect your personal data, electronic storage is secure and personal data are sent using appropriate secure technologies.

 **Please note:** For legal purposes, the original [Arabic version of this privacy policy](https://adhd.org.sa/?p=7724) takes precedence over this English translation.

Last updated by Jeremy Varnham on 12 July 2023 and currently under active review. Previous versions of the privacy policy may be found at: [Privacy Policy Archive](https://adhd.org.sa/en/privacy-policy/privacy-policy-archive/)

**At the Saudi ADHD Society, your privacy is our commitment.**

Should you have any questions or concerns, please contact: [\[email protected\]](https://adhd.org.sa/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

The Saudi ADHD Society is a registered NGO with license 474 from the Saudi Ministry of Human Resources and Social Development.

MS-SymbolLockup  

Sign In

The Saudi ADHD Society is a registered NGO with license 474 from the Saudi Ministry of Human Resources and Social Development.

MS-SymbolLockup  

Sign In
